dieantwoord.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy Policy - Futureshirts

Effective: _May 25, 2018._

Futureshirts, LLC. _("Futureshirts", the "Company," "we," "us," or "our")_ know that our users care how their personally identifiable information _("Information")_ is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and disclose Information when you use any of our Services, including but not limited to:

  * Company websites, webstores, pages, sites, accounts or channels accessible through any Internet or wireless enabled device
  * Mobile applications
  * Ticketing and live event gatherings we host or sponsor
  * Company online platforms and related offerings
  * Websites, pages or apps created or powered by the Futureshirts

Any material changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page prior to the change becoming effective. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

Certain Futureshirts sites will have a separate privacy policy governing that site's collection and use of your information, so please carefully review such separate privacy policy before using that site.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed by sending us a detailed message to one of the following addresses:

**Email** : [privacy@futureshirts.com](mailto:privacy@futureshirts.com)

Futureshirts  
Attn: Privacy / Legal Department  
3720 Keystone Ave.  
Nashville, TN 37211

### Information We May Collect From You

When you use the Site or contact us by e-mail, social media, SMS, telephone, or other methods, we may collect and process the following data about you:

Information You Give Us, Including:

  * Forms filled out by you on the Site
  * Content of correspondence with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise
  * Site registration
  * Subscriptions or orders placed on the Site
  * Mailing address and payment information from orders placed by you on the Site or Webstore
  * Participation in discussion boards or other social media functions on the Site
  * Entering a competition, promotion or survey
  * Reporting a problem or requesting support for the Site

The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, date of birth, payment information, personal description, photographs or images or comments.

### Information We Collect About You

With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:

  * Technical information, including IP address, login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform
  * Information about your visit, including the full URL clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time)
  * Pages you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page

We may also collect information our about your devices (including phones, computers or other devices) where you access and visit our Sites. Such information may include unique device identifiers and mobile network information (including phone number), IP address, language and time zone, operating system, hardware version, device locations (including specific geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth or WiFi signals).

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We also work with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, social networks such as Facebook and Twitter, search information providers, credit reference agencies, third parties who enable sign on functionality and social network integration) and may receive information about you from them.

If you choose to use features on this Site that connect to your online profiles, accounts or services (including social media accounts) (“Connected Accounts”), we may collect any information that you permit through your settings on those Connected Accounts. For example, if you log in to our site using your Facebook account and choose to allow Facebook to share your profile with us, we may collect that information. Information we receive from Connected Accounts includes email address, first and last name, location (hometown and country), gender, date of birth, likes, posts or other social activity. Please review your Connected Account privacy settings to control what information is provided to us through this option.

### How Your Information May Be Used

We may use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To help us respond to your queries
  * To provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about or that we feel may interest you
  * To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site about goods or services that may interest you or them
  * To provide or permit third parties to provide targeted advertising via websites you visit about goods or services that you may find interesting
  * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you
  * To track the progress and number of entries in competitions and promotions.
  * To allow you to interact with our Site, for example by posting comments or to share information from our Site on third party social media platforms
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us
  * To manage your access to the services or notify you about changes to the services
  * To comply with legal and regulatory requirements
  * To administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes
  * To improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer
  * As part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure
  * We may combine information we receive from other sources with information you give to us and information we collect about you (including information in relation to your devices). We may use this combined information for the purposes set out above

### How We May Disclose Your Information

We may share your personal data with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you in order to provide you with a product or service
  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors to provide you with information about promotions and offers
  * Advertisers, advertising networks and social networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We may also use aggregate and other information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our Site
  * Third parties when you consent to or request such sharing.
  * We may disclose your personal data to third parties
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Futureshirts, LLC, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction
  * To any other third party where lawful

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk.

### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site. For detailed information on the cookies and other technologies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookies Policy below.

### Social Media and Other Third Parties That Provide Content, Advertising or Functionality On Our Services

Some of the content, advertising and functionality on our Site may be provided by third parties that are not affiliated with us. For example, you may have the opportunity to log in to our Site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal data with us. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Third-party advertisers also may have a presence on our Sites. These and other third parties may collect or receive certain information about your use of our Sites, including through the use of cookies and other Internet technologies, and this information may be collected over time and combined with information collected across different websites and online services.

Some of these companies participate in industry-developed programs designed to provide consumers choices about whether to receive targeted advertising. Please visit the websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative, Digital Advertising Alliance, and European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.

### Children

This Site is not directed toward children (as defined by local law) nor does Futureshirts knowingly collect information from children (as defined by local law) without parental consent except where in compliance with applicable laws.

### Your Rights

You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to object to or request the restriction of processing of your personal data, and to request access to, rectification, erasure, and portability of your own personal data by contacting us as described in the “Contact” section. We may require you to prove your identity with approved identification if you request this information.

You may also be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your personal data infringes applicable law.

You are responsible for keeping your information current and up-to-date. You may update your information by contacting us as described in the “Contact” section.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us as described in the “Contact” section.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California residents may opt out of having their personally identifiable information shared with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes by contacting us as described in the “Contact” section.

### Links To Third Party Sites

Our Site, our newsletters and other communications may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

### Cookies Policy

Our Site uses cookies and other similar technologies (as described below) to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site, allows us to improve our Site and provide you with tailored content and advertising.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

You can find more information about the types of cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below:

### Strictly Necessary

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to browse our Site and use its features. The information collected by these cookies relate to the operation of our Site, for example website scripting language and security tokens to maintain secure areas of our Site

### Performance / Analytics

These cookies collect anonymous information about how you use our Site, for example which pages you visit most often, whether you receive any error messages, and how you arrived at our Site. Information collected by these cookies is used only to improve your use of our Site and never to identify you. These cookies are sometimes placed by third-party providers of web traffic analysis services, such as Google Analytics.

### Functionality

These cookies remember choices you make, for example the country you visit our Site from, your language and any changes you have made to text size or other parts of web pages that you can customize, in order to improve your experience of our Site and to make your visits more tailored and enjoyable. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and cannot be used to track your browsing activity on other websites.

### Targeting or Advertising

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits and inferred interests in order to make advertising more relevant to you. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert, as well as to measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. These cookies are usually placed by third-party advertising networks. They remember the other websites that you visit and this information is shared with third-party organizations, for example advertisers.

### Social Media

These cookies allow you to share what you’ve been doing on our Site with social media organizations such as Facebook and Twitter. These cookies are not within our control. Please refer to the privacy policies of these organizations for how their cookies work.

Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

Most internet browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies. However, if you want to refuse or delete any cookies (or similar technologies), please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to block or delete cookies. Please note you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of our Site, including certain personalized features, if you delete or disable cookies.

For more information on managing cookies, please go to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), or visit [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) which has further information about behavioral advertising and online privacy.

### Web Beacons

We, or our third-party partners, may employ a software technology called web beacons (also known as pixels) which helps us understand what content is effective, for example by counting the number of users who have visited these pages, and to understand usage patterns. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to let us know when content is viewed. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded on web pages, ads, and e-mail. We, or our third-party partners, may tie the information gathered by web beacons to the other information we collect about you.

In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies as described above, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks and vendors, audience segment providers, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative, Digital Advertising Alliance, or European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.
